A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1989-039
162 Cubic Feet 165 boxes
The Fries Textile Plant Records includes correspondence, production data, personnel ledgers, photographs, legal and financial materials, internal reports, blueprints, and other administrative materials. The collection provides a complete history of the company's operations, from its founding at the turn of the twentieth century until its closure in the 1980s.
Fries Textile Plant (Fries, Va.)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research with the exception of records containing HIPAA-protected, sensitive, or personally identifiable information. These records are noted in the file-level description. Contact Virginia Tech Special Collections for more information.
Acquisition Information
The Fries Textile Plant Records were deposited with Special Collections in 1989.
Ownership of the collection was transferred to Virginia Tech in 2016.
Additional blueprints and slides were transferred to Virginia Tech in December 2016 and July 2019.
Administrative History
In 1903, Colonel Francis Henry Fries founded the town of Fries and constructed a textile plant in Grayson County, Virginia. Fries was president of the Washington Mills Company as well as Wachovia Bank, for some time. He used his business and political connections to build a spur to a main branch of the Norfolk and Western Railroad and to construct a dam on the New River to generate power for the mill. The Washington Mills Company owned nearly every building in the town, which flourished in the early twentieth century with a population of over 1,700 in 1910. By 1929, there were four textile mills in Grayson County, and Washington Mills in Fries was the largest, employing as many as 600 people.
Employment at Washington Mills peaked after World War II with over 1,200 workers. For decades, the mill had cutting edge equipment and competed nationally with other textile production facilities. By the 1980s, the company faced overseas competition and the need to modernize the plant. In 1988, company leaders chose to close the plant, which at that time employed only a few hundred workers. Sources:
Bond, Avery, and Martha Nichols, comps. and eds. A History of the Town of Fries, Virginia. Collinsville, VA: Collinsville Printing Company, 1977.
"Historical Background, Town of Fries, Compiled in 1953 for 50th Anniversary of Fries," box 34, Fries Textile Plant Records, Special Collections, Virginia Tech.
National Register of Historic Places. "Fries Boarding Houses, VDHR#220-5015," September 14, 2007.
https://www.dhr.virginia.gov/historic-registers/220-5015/
Scope and Content
This collection includes correspondence, ledgers, production records, employee records, photographs, fabric samples, and other items documenting the history of the town and plant from their creation in the eary 1900s to the close of the mill in 1988.
Series I. Company Files and Series II. Correspondence mainly document the day-to-day running of the mill, highlighting relationships with other local and national businesses in fields such as textiles, factory machinery, coal, insurance, and construction. These records also illustrate some aspects of the lives of the mill employees.
Series III. Financial Records document the more quantifiable aspect of the business through invoices, pay records, and account balance books, showing the health and trajectory of the company over time.
Series IV. Personnel Records convey the activity of the mill by recording the number of each type of employee, how much they worked, and when, as well as some glimpses into the personal lives of the mill workers.
Series V. Production Materials more concretely illustrate the output of the mill through fabric samples and reports of production versus cost over time.
Series VI. Legal Records show how the mill grew and evolved over time in relation to the community in which it operated.
Series VII. Blueprints show how the mill buildings themselves were conceived, built, and changed from 1900-1974, when the last major renovations were completed.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by type of material into the following series:
Series I. Company Files
Series II. Correspondence
Series III. Financial Records
Series IV. Personnel Records
Series V. Production Materials
Series VI. Legal Records
Series VII. Blueprints
Index Terms
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; Textile manufacturers; Textile industry--Employees; Textiles; Company towns
Geographic Terms:
Fries (Va.); Grayson County (Va.)
Organizations:
Fries Textile Plant (Fries, Va.)
Contents List
- Series I: Company Files, 1908-1979
  - Victor Ring Traveler Co. #1, February 1927- August 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Virginia (Commonwealth), January 1927- January 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Culvert Corp., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Iron Coal and Coke Co., 1927-1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Bridge and Iron Co., 1930-1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Mfr's. Ass'n, 1927-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Metal Mfg Co., 1930-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Va. State-Wide Safety Conference, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Tree Farms May, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Walker Electric Co., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Walbuck Crayon Co., 1930-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The James Walker Co., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - P. Wall Mfg. Co., 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Wallace and Tierman, February 1930- November 1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - D. S. Walton and Co., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Waltham Watch Co., 1934-1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Edgar J. Ward's Sons, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Warmer Flooring Co. Inc., 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - E. H. Warrick June, 1929-1933 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Jules Racine and Co., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Radiator Specialty Co. Charlotte, N.C., 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Radford Limestone Co., 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Railway Express Agency (See Westinghouse Elec. and Mfg Co.), April 21, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Raleigh Smokeless Fuel Co., 1932-1937 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ralli Brothers, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Ramseur Broom Wks, 1927-1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rawley and Apperson Co., September 1934- May 1937 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ray Pressure Snubber Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - H. Harley Read, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Realty Bond Sup. Co., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - C. A. Reavis, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Red Jacket Consolidated Coal and Coke Co., March 1929 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Reed Mfg. Co., 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Arthur Reid, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Reid-Way Corp., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Chas. H. Roeisig, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Reliance Steel Corp., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Remington Rand Business Service Inc., 1928-1937 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Remington Typewriter Co., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Reeves Pulley Co., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - R. J. Reynolds Tob. Co., 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - J. E. Rhoods and Son, May 1927- December 1940 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rhode Island Warp Stop Equip. Co., 19301935 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Riverside and Dan River Cotton Mills., 1929-1940 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The Rhodes Press, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Richmond Abattoir, 1927-1930 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Richards-Wilcox, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - J. F. Richardson, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rigler Engineering Co., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - G. A. Ring, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - T. C. Ripley, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Dallas Rippie, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - T. C. Rippey, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Riverside and Dan River Cotton Mills, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Risdon Mfg. Co., 1927 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Roanoke Drug Co., 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Roanoke Glass Co., 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Roanoke Hardware Co., 1928-1937 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Roanoke-Webster Brick Co., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Roanoke Welding Co., 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Robbins and Myers, Inc., December 1936- September 1940 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Roberts Filter Mfg. Co., 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Ben Robinson, Jr., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Rockwood Mfg. Co., 1931-1934 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Saco-Lowell Shops, 1927-1940 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Joseph L. Ryerson and Son, Inc., July 1938- July 1940 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - The R. U. V. Co. New York City, 1927-1930 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Russel and Erwin Mfg. Co., September 1927- February 1940 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Rumsey Pump Co., 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Rural Home Service Station, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - The Rubberoid Co., 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - The Royal Typewrite Co., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Royal Metal Mfg. Co., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - B. S. Roy and Son, December 1930- April 1940 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Clayton Rotenberry, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - J. H. Ross and Co., May-November 1938 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - The Root Mfg. Co Bristol, Conn., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Rome Wire Co., 1927 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Rogers Paint Store, 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Roessler and Hasslacher Chemical Co., March 25, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Rockford Bolt Co., 1927 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Seaboard Steel and Iron Co., September 1935- February 1938 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Scott Paper Company, 1932-1934 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Chas. A Schieren Co., 1934-1938 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - S. M. Schwab Jr. and Co, October 24, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Scarborough Chevrolet Co., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Saunders Chevrolet Sales, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Sash Door and Glass Corp, July 18, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Sanitary Plumbing and Heating Co., May 10, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Sanders Bros. Co, 1927-1940 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Sampson Paint and Color Co., October 1930- April 1934 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Samson-United Corp, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Salisbury Mfg. Co., 1927-1931 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Salem Foundry and Mche Works, May 25, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - The Safety Grinding Wheel and Mche Co., May 8, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - The Safety Equipment Co., 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - John A. Roebling's and Sons Co., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Appalachian Elec. Power Co., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Parker Wire Goods Co., 1928-1930 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Parks Woodworking Mche. Co., 1928-1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - J. M. Parsons, 1927-1940 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pasteur Vaccine Laboratories, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Carlos Patton, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - John M. Patton, 1929-1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - W. A. Patton, 1930-1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - E. P. Payne, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Paymaster: Wash. Mills, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pease Woodwork Co., 1937 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Frank Pearman, 1934-1939 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Garnett Pearman, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pearse- Slaughter Belting Co., 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Peaslee and Gaulbert Co., July 1927- January 1933 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Peerless Paper Specialty Co., 1932 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pendleton Construction Co., 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - S. B. Penick and Co., January 25, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania Pump and Compression Co., August- September 1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Percy Heilner and Son, February 10, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Penry-Attchison Printing Co., 1930-1945 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Joel S. Perkins and Son, February 1937- June 1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Perry-Mann Elec. Co., 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Perryman Bros. Lumber Co., 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Peterson Hydraulic Sewer Flsher Co., 1928-1935 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Pfaff's Inc., 1932-1940 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Philadelphia Belting Co., 1928-1935 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Phila. Felt Co., 1933-1940 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dr. J. C. Phipps (folder 1 of 2), 1932-1940 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dr. J. C. Phipps (folder 2 of 2), 1932-1940 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pittman-Moore Co., 1932-1939 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Pless Elec. Co., 1936-1940 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Plews Oiler Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Pocahantas Coal Sales Co. Cincinnatti O., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Poe Hdwe and Supply Co., October 1936- February 1934 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Albert Pick Co. Chicago, Ill., 1935 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Piedmont Motor Express Co., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Piedmont Sheet Metal Co., 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Pierce, Butler and Pierce Co., May 1936- December 1938 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Pine Hall Brick and Pipe Co., June 1934- January 1940 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Pioneer Instrument Co., 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pittsburgh Equitable Meter Co., 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., 1928-1939 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Platt Iron Works, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Pleasants Hdwe Co., 1934 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Connie Poe, 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - R. F. Poe, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Poland Soap Wks, 1927-1940 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Poole Chevrolet Co., 1930-1936 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Howard Porter, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - McPorter, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - The Frederick Post Co., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Postal-Telegraph and Cable Co., March 3, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Powers and Anderson Dental Co., October 17, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Power Brake Co., 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Power Equipment Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Precision Gear and Mche Co., May- July 1937 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - The Prest-O-Lite Co., 1927-1931 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Price Hardware Co., 1928 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Protection Prod. Mfg. Co., 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Public Service Elec. Sup. Co., 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Pulaski Engineering Works, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Pulaski Foundry and Mchy Co., September 1927- January 1932 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Pulaski Iron Co., 1931 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Pulmosan Safety Equipment Corp., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Pyrene Mfg. Co., 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Garnet Taylor, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Taylor-Colquitt Co., 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Halsey W. Taylor Co., 1927-1939 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Teck Mfg. Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Tennessee Eastman Corp, 1934-1940 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Tennessee Mill and Mine Sup. Co., August 24, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Tennessee Nursery Co., 1935 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - The Textile Mill Sup. Co. #5, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - The Terrell Machine Co., 1927-1940 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - W.O. and W. M. Talcott Inc., February 9, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Taylor Instrument Co., 1929-1940 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - The Texas Company, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Textile Apron Co., 1935 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - The Textile Mill Sup. Co., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - The Textile Mill Sup. Co. 4, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - The Textile Mill Sup. Co. 3, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Textile Mill Sup. Co. #2, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Textile Mill Sup. Co. #1, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Textile Paper Products Inc., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - The Textile Specialty Co., 1930-1940 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Texwood Mfg. Co., 1929 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Thompson Mfg. Company, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Charlie Thomas, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Ed Thomas Fries VA, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - P. N. Thorpe and Co., February- October 1937 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Three States Coal Co., 1927 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - J. T. Tice, 1935-1938 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Lonnie Tickle, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Tidewater Sup. Co., 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Tidewater Sup. Co. #2, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Tidewater Sup. Co., August 1927- December 1932 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Tildesley Coal Co., May- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The John S. Tilley Ladders Co., July 1934- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - J. C. Todd, Inc., January 25, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Toledo Scale Co. A. B. Camper, Agent, June 1927- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Enrique Touceda C. E., November 1934- August 1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tower-Binford Elec. Mfg. Co., January 1927- March 1931 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Town of Fries, June 12, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - C. J. Towers and Son, April 1936- October 1937 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Transylvania Tanning Co., February 1932- March 1933 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Trane Co., February 10, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Transmission Ball Bearing Co, January- July 1933 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Trico Fuse Co., February 10, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Trinacria Specialty Mfg. Co., November 1935- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tristate Elec. Sup. Co., August 1932- April 1940 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Triple T. Tempering Compound Co., February 1934- May 1940 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Trumbull Elec Co, April 12, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - J. M. Tull Rubber and Supply Co., December 1930- January 1931 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Tuttle, W. H. Electric Co., June 6, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Twin Oaks Motor Co., September 9, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Twin City Elec. Repair Shop, January 1930- September 1932 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Twin County Motor Co. Galax Va., November 1930- July 1933 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Twin City Novelty Co., December 21, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Ultramarine Co., April 1927- November 1939 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Underwood-Elliott Fisher Co., September 1934- January 1940 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Union Stationery Corp., April 25, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Unique Printed Products Co., Inc., October 25, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Union Twist Drill Co., November 25, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - United-Carr Fastner Co., January 25, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - United Cigarette Mche. Co., November 1934- June 1938 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - United Collieries, Inc., September 25, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - United Seal Co., April 27, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - United States Gauge Co., February- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - U-File-Em Binder Mfg. Co., August 1936 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - C. L. Upchurch and Sons, May 1934- August 1938 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - US Cotton Machinery Co., February- March 1932 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Upjohn Company, June 1931- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - US Bobbin and Shuttle Co., January 1929- February 1936 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - The U.S. Elec. Tool Co., May 10, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - U. S. Ring Traveler Co., September 1933- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - U. S. Gutta Percha Paint Co., November 1934- September 1936 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - United States Rubber Co., August 10, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Union Mfg. Co., March 10, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Union Water Meter Co., April 28, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Utilities Elec. Mchry. Co., July 25, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Utilities Service Co., June 25, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Valentine's Meat Juice Co., April- September 1940 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - J. A. Vance Co., February 1928- April 1940 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Vass-Kapp Hardware Co., May 1930- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - B. M. Vaughan, November 1929- November 1932 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Fred Vaughan, October 1929- December 1930 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Jack Vaughan, December 14, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - H. E. Vaughan, December 9, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - J. W. Vaughan Jr., November 9, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - R. H. Vaughan, May 25, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - L. J. Vaughan, January 1933- Nov. 1936 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Reid Vaughan, January 1935- January 1937 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - W. F. Vaughan, December 23, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Veeder-Root Co., February 1928- February 1940 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - J. W. Venoble, November 1929- June 1930 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Vermont Tap and Die Corp., February 9, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - V. V. Fittings Co., October- December 1931 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Vicco Fuel Corp., March 23, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Victor Mfg. Co., January- March 1934 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Vick Paint Co., April- November 1934 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Victor Ring Traveler Co. #2, January 1931- June 1934 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous "A", February 1940- August 1941 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Abington Textile Machinery Works, March- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - E. P Alexander and Son, June- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Aluminum Line, February- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - American Cotton Co-Operative Association, January- February 1940 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - The American Cotton Mfgr's Association, January- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - American- Hawaiian SS Co., February- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - American Optical Copany, February- May 1940 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - American Water Works Association, July- August 1940 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - American Wool and Cotton Reporter, March- April 1940 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Co., May 1940 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Application Letters, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Arista Mills Company, May- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, June- August 1940 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Arrow Steamship Line, February- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Ashworth Bros. Inc., May- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Atlas Supply Co, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Miscellaneous "B", 1940 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bahan Textile Machinery Co, January- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Bahnson- Spaugh, Reid- Fuloch, etc. (folder 1 of 2), July- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Bahnson- Spaugh, Reid- Fuloch, etc. (folder 2 of 2), January- June 1940 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - The Bahnson Co, February 22, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Banner Fuel Corporation, December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Barber-Asphalt Corp., January- October 1940 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Barber-Colman Company, January- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Barber Steamship Co., February- April 1940 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - W. F. John Barnes Co., January 1940 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - R. L. Batteiger Co., November- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - J. T. Beaty Machine Co., March- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Belks Dept. Stores, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Belknap Hardware and Mfg. Co., April- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Bemis Bros. Bag Co., February- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Billings and Spencer Company, August- November 1940 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Booze Truck Lines, February- September 1940 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Borden Mills, Inc., February- November 1940 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    This material is restricted for 75 years due to personally identifiable information. Contact Special Collections for additional information.
  - Borne, Scrymser Co., February- May 1940 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Bowditch and Company, March- April 1940 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - The Bright Brooks Lumber Co., May- August 1940 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Brooklyn Perfex Corporation, January- February 1940 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Brownlee-Johnson Lbr. Co., February- August 1940 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Brown-Rogers-Dixson Co., March- April 1940 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Burroughs Adding Machine Co., January- September 1940 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Mr. J. E. Bunton (see Chesapeake Paper Stock Co), October 1940 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Butler Iron and Steel Co., March- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Miscellaneous "C", February- December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - The Cardwell Machine Company, February- August 1940 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Mr. Joe L. Carlton, March- October 1940 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Carolina Bagging Co., February- July 1940 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Carrier Corporation, January- May 1940 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Cauthorne Paper Company, March- October 1940 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Celanese Corporation of America, December 1940 (Box 3, Folder 117)